<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Solar>
    <Earth>                          Earth

Diameter: 12742km
Distance to sun: 150 millin km
    </Earth>
    <Venus>                           Venus
Diameter: 12104km    
Venus is the second planet from the Sun
It has the longest rotation period: 243 days
Rotates in the opposite direction to most other planets.
    </Venus>
    <Mercury>                        Mercury 
Diameter: 4879km  
The smallest and innermost planet in the Solar System.

Orbital period: 87.97 days, is the shortest of all the planets in the Solar System.      
    </Mercury>
    <Mars>                           Mars
Diameter: 12104km  
Mars is a terrestrial planet with a thin atmosphere
It is the fourth planet from the Sun and the second-smallest planet.
The reddish iron oxide prevalent on its surface gives it a reddish appearance     
    </Mars>
    <Jupiter>                        Jupiter
Jupiter is a gas giant planet(139822km), primarily composed of hydrogen. 
The outer atmosphere is segregated into several bands, resulting in turbulence and storms.
A prominent result is the Great Red Spot, a giant storm that is known to have existed since at least the 17th century
    </Jupiter>
    <Saturn>                         Saturn
Saturn is a gas giant with an average radius(116464km) about nine times that of Earth.
The core of Saturn is surrounded by a deep layer of metallic hydrogen
Wind speeds on Saturn can reach 1,800 km/h (1,100 mph), higher than on Jupiter
    </Saturn>
    <Uranus>                         Uranus
The "ice giant". It has the coldest planetary atmosphere in the Solar System, with a minimum temperature of −224 °C
It's axis of rotation is tilted sideways(97.77°), nearly into the plane of its solar orbit.
Wind speeds can reach 900 km/h.
    </Uranus>
    <Neptune>                        Neptune
The densest giant planet in the solar system, one of the "ice giants".

Traces of methane in the outermost regions in part account for it's blue appearance.
Neptune has the strongest wind (2100 km/h) in the solar system.
    </Neptune>
</Solar>